The war was over and the world was falling in love again.
New York, New York is a romance, drama, music film directed by Martin Scorsese.
An egotistical saxophone player and a young singer meet on V-J Day and embark upon a
strained and rocky romance, even as their careers begin a long uphill climb.
Francine Evans, played by Liza Minnelli.
Jimmy Doyle, played by Robert De Niro.
Tony Harwell, played by Lionel Stander.
Paul Wilson, played by Barry Primus.
Bernice Bennett, played by Mary Kay Place.
Nicky, played by George Memmoli.
New York, New York is a 1977 American musical romantic comedy film directed by Martin Scorsese
from a screenplay by Earl Mac Rauch and Mardik Martin, based on a story by Rauch.
John Kander and Fred Ebb wrote several songs for the film, including "New
York, New York", which became a worldwide hit and standard.
A tribute to Scorsese's hometown of New York City, the film stars Liza
Minnelli and Robert De Niro as a pair of musicians and lovers.
The film explores themes of new york city, jazz, jazz
singer or musician, saxophonist, musical.
The tone is dark and emotional.